iamplify.com 2008-05-03

# iAmplify - I amplify, do you?

iAmplify, LLC ("iAmplify") is very sensitive to the privacy concerns of iAmplify customers and visitors to our website (the "Site") at www.iamplify.com (collectively, the "iAmplify users"). This iAmplify Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") explains our practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal and non-personal information provided by iAmplify users. By visiting the Site or signing up for our services including free services, iAmplify users signify their assent to this Privacy Policy. 

**Collection of Information**

**Personal Information**

In general, we only collect personal information from iAmplify users when they voluntarily submit it to us. Personal information that we may collect includes, but is not necessarily limited to, first and last name, telephone number, physical address, e-mail address, fitness profile information, payment method, credit card number, credit card expiration date, and password. 

**Non-Personal Information**

Certain non-personal information about Site visits is recorded by the standard operation of the Site. The non-personal information that we collect includes the type of operating system in use (e.g., Macintosh or Windows), the type of browser being used by the iAmplify user (e.g., Netscape or Internet Explorer), IP address, and the domain name from which visitors accessed the Site (e.g., Yahoo.com). 

In addition, we may collect information about iAmplify users' browsing behavior, such as the date and time they visit the Site, the areas or pages of our Site that they visit, the amount of time spent viewing the Site, the number of times the iAmplify user returns to the Site, and other click-stream data (collectively, the "Browsing Behavior Information"). We may use cookies (small text files that are stored on iAmplify users' computers when they access our Site) to collect Browsing Behavior Information. We may associate information we collect via cookies with the personal information we collect about iAmplify users. 

iAmplify users are always free to decline cookies, but in doing so they may not be able to use certain features of the Site. The "help" segment of the toolbar on most browsers explains how to configure a browser to not accept new cookies, how to have the browser inform a user when they receive a new cookie, and how to erase cookies from their hard drives. 

**Use of Information**

iAmplify may use information collected from iAmplify users (the "User Information") for any of the following purposes (1) to facilitate online purchases; (2) to fulfill orders; (3) to send marketing and other communications to iAmplify users; (4) to conduct internal reviews of the Site (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to the Site); (5) to help us better understand iAmplify users use of the Site; (6) to respond to specific requests from iAmplify users; and (7) to protect the security or integrity of the Site Non-personal information will be used for purposes of conducting internal reviews of the Site, monitoring the Site, and providing an enhanced online experience for iAmplify users. 

**Disclosure of Information**

iAmplify may transfer or otherwise disclose the User Information to (i) content providers ("Amplifiers") and an Amplifier's publisher or other media distributor (together with Amplifiers, "Content Partners") when the content is provided by such Content Partners, so that the Content Partners can send iAmplify users relevant promotional communications about their respective products and services and to (ii) iAmplify's employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, consultants, and other business partners and associates, service providers, and suppliers, if the disclosure will enable that party to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for iAmplify.. iAmplify may also disclose User Information if required to do so by law, in response to judicial process, and, as permitted under provisions of law, to provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on a matter related to public safety. 

Unless expressly allowed under this policy, iAmplify may only share, transfer or otherwise disclose the User Information to third parties in bulk or aggregate format, with no personally identifiable information included. 

**Security of Information**

iAmplify maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your personal information. We allow access to personal information only to persons and entities engaging in activities provided for by this Privacy Policy. We use Secure Socket Layer technology, among other technologies, to protect any credit card information you provide us. 

**Personally Identifiable Information of Children**

iAmplify's Site is directed towards adults, and sells some products that are for children to adults. You may only register for and use the Site if you are 18 or over. If you are a parent or guardian and your child's personally identifiable information has been collected by iAmplify and you wish to review such information, prevent its use by iAmplify pursuant to this Privacy Policy or request our deletion of it, please contact us by email at [customerservice@iamplify.com](mailto:customerservice@iamplify.com).

**Unforeseen Circumstances**

In the event that iAmplify or any of its assets are acquired by a third party, personal information acquired by us may be one of the assets transferred.

**Acceptance of Privacy Terms & Conditions **

By visiting the Site or the associated services, iAmplify users agree to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. To the extent that any of the third-party sites accessible through the Site have privacy practices different from those stated in this Privacy Policy, those third-party privacy practices govern the collection and use of information iAmplify users provide when visiting those sites. iAmplify is not responsible for the policies, content, and practices of other companies. 

**Changes To This Privacy Statement**

On occasion, it may be necessary for iAmplify to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. To ensure that iAmplify users are aware of current privacy practices, we recommend that they check the Site periodically. 

**Contact Us**

For questions regarding the iAmplify Online Privacy Policy or other issues, please email us at [help@iamplify.com](https://mail.google.com/mail?view=cm&tf=0&to=help@iamplify.com&su=Suggestion%20From%20iAmplify%20Customer&body=Here%20are%20my%20ideas%20for%20iAmplify:%0A%0ANew%20Content:%0AWebsite%20Functionality:%0AOther:).
